### Sean Purtill

### Resume

My professional experience is suited for supporting a software development team, with emphasis in adaptability, reliability and team leadership.

Visit www.seandoescode.ca to view my online portfolio.

### 60 Panatella St NW Calgary, T3K 0M3 587 572 6152 sean.does.code @gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Winsport Canada,** Calgary — *Event Set Up, Team Manager* 2014 - 2017

- ~ As Set up Team Lead, I coordinate the on-site logistics with the Events department for small corporate events to 3000+ guest festivals. ~ Drawing on my 10+ years of experience in the hospitality industry, this challenging role is a combination of customer service, operations management, project planning and supervising teams of ranging from 3 to 20 staff
- ~ Transitioned 3 on-site Restaurant facilities from using disposable cloths to kitchen cloths washable in-house, saving 90% in costs, and vastly reducing unnecessary waste
- ~ Designing an intricately welded frame for moving chairs increasing work speed by 300%, particularly useful during time-critical events

# **Good Shepherd Eye Clinic,** Swaziland— *Project Coordinator* 2013

- ~ Worked the medical and clerical staff to modernize the administrative side of the of the clinic operations, focusing on patient data management, procurement, inventory management, and administrative accounting
- ~ Coordinated the launch of a patient database in three rural African clinics, including government hospitals, across Swaziland, which transitioned handwritten medical records to electronic records

## **Bell Canada**, Mississauga— *Project Coordinator Intern* 2012 to 2013

 $\sim$  As an intern in the project management office, I focused on improving the internship program while meeting goals set for our department. This was achieved through document management, vendor relations, communication system development, and inventory management

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CCS, and Javascript

Java

C#

Python

SQL

Agile Methodologies

#### **EDUCATION**

Southern
Alberta
Institute of
Technology,
Calgary —
Object
Oriented
Software
Development

2017 to 2018

Trent
University,
Peterborough—
Business
Administration
and Philosophy
Honours

2006 to 2010